Curriculum Vitae

CLIFF ODHIAMBO

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Phone No.: 0724 104 677

E-mail: cokumu75@gmail.com
Online Portfolio: https://talk2klif.github.io/

ABOUT ME

I've been a web designer for 3 years. I've learned many things about web design since starting out in this industry, and the things I've learned have helped me develop processes that benefit everyone involved in the projects I work on. I am eager to acquire more knowledge, skills and expertise through guidance and my own initiative to compliment my output.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1st December 2015 – To date PAGE ONE SEO & Online Marketing

Duties include:

- Assist in planning the new site development.
- Design and develop sites and email marketing asset.
- Maintaining clients' mailboxes.
- Maintaining the existing websites.
- Implementing SEO in all static websites.
- Train the new employees.
- Handle company-client communication
- Enhancing the look, functionality and appearance of a website
- Fixing problems encountered in the functioning of the website
- Creating client email campign newsletters (HTML)

December 2012 – January 2014 - Uchumi Supermarket Ltd.

Duties included:

- Ensure quality customer service
- Data entry
- Shelf stocker

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

| 2014 - 2015 | MarketNairobits Trust Diploma in Web and Graphic Design/Development SEO and Online Marketing |
|------------------|--|
| 2007 - 2010 | MarketVihiga High School ■ Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (C+) |
| 2004 - 2006 | Wangu Primary School ● Kenya Certificate of Primary Education |
| TECHNICAL SKILLS | , |

- Web Design: Visual Layout, Graphical User Interface, Navigational Design, Responsive Web Design, Email Campaigns
- Web Development: WordPress, Joomla, HTML5 /CSS3
- Software: Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Illustrator, Microsoft Office, MailChimp, Vertical Response

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Innovative thinker and eager to try new things
- Excellent communication skills for client facing meetings
- Efficient in communicating well in writing and verbal both
- Able to prioritize work according to importance
- Able to work under high pressure

REFEREES

1. REBECCA KARUMA

- Senior Scrum Master PAGE ONE SEO & Online Marketing
- rebecca@page-one.co.ke

2. CHARLES KABUE

- Senior Back End Web Developer PAGE ONE SEO & Online Marketing
- charles@page-one.co.ke

3. ISAAC BRIAN OKELLO

- Senior Front End Web Developer Squad Digital
- isaackokello@gmail.com